Yeah.
And what I can to close this valley of corruption.
Time to see if the card affords Will let me pass over the mountains.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
Thank you.
Yeah,
yeah,
yes.
Sounds a fight.
Something attempted.
Culture foot.
Okay,
a corruptor.
God!
So
next time.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Football
starting
you were.
Hello,
Diet.
Yeah.
I'll find a use for you.
Truly.
The sun shines upon us this day.
It wasn't the son risking its ass down here.
Girl approach.
So will you open the gate for me now?
You heard her.
Open the gates and send word to Captain Balon.
Where you headed, Girl?
West to Meridian.
Yeah.
The way of broken stones is a hard run.
Even in the best of times.
You might wanna have a word with Captain Balon.
He came from Meridian not long ago.
You find him in the fort on a balcony to the left, overlooking the valley.
Okay.
Thanks.
We're the ones who should be thanking you for taking down those machines walking light.
Nora,
always
relax.
We all have our place in the order.
Nothing but trouble.
That's all there is in but new glance.
Okay,
Don't ask me where to go If you're lost in the garden of the town Crier.
Captain Blonde.
I have questions for you.
First about another nor a woman who might have come through here and second about the trail to Meridian.
What can I expect on the way?
Well, it was definitely another Nora.
Nowhere.
I forget that she caused an incident.
As for what to expect on the trail?
Nothing good.
More machines all the time in our scouts report corruption that way as well.
So much for sealing things off.
Keep to the roads.
They're safe enough.
No.
After what you did at the gate, I'll wager you don't scare easy.
It's a good quality.
I could put it to use if you don't mind a quick John back east.
Now it's bold of me to ask a favor after you just did one.
But I can offer you answers in return.
There's anything you need to know about this Sunday.
Um What do you need, Captain?
I sent several patrols east when we got word of corrupted machines there.
I let them confirm my fears.
So I seal the gates.
But it looks like we left some men behind when they were closed.
Willie, tell him what happened.
Machines attacked us near an abandoned Nora village service.
Look here.
Told us to pull back.
Then I lost sight of the others.
Never seen a nor a woman before.
Soldier.
Have some respect.
Report to her.
Not to me.
Look here.
Always stresses reporting back.
So that's what I did.
I felt terrible about leaving them behind.
Now that the gates were open again, I can send someone after them.
Can't you send more soldiers to find the missing men?
What about will lead here most.
Nora still don't take well to the site of card your armor.
Officially, it's a risk to send patrols so close to your sacred land.
I prefer not to do that again.
But heading that way won't be a problem for you.
Please say yes.
What was that, soldier?
Nothing, sir.
I'll see what I can do about your missing men.
I would be grateful, but not as grateful is Walid.
You hear that, lunkhead?
You might be off the hook every season.
The machines, Rammasun, kicking up one
raised machines.
Where?
Their shamans Damn nonsense.
It's worse.
Mhm,
Yes.
Mhm.
black smoke, red tatters.
More bandits like the ones that doubles Thirst,
please.
Yeah.
Okay.
So much for being careful.
Yeah.
Okay.
No.
All right.
Yes.
Mhm.
Yeah,
but I just
Uh huh.
Yeah,
I just
This
e
I just
right.
Oh,
I was looking for
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Okay.
It's really
okay.
E.
Okay.
Why?
For Miranda.
Okay.
Oh, sorry.
Oh,
Okay.
That's
yeah,
yeah.
Mhm e No, I'm here now.
Yeah,
yes.
Mhm.
Oh,
just
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah,
Fine,
please.
A little help here, please.
Right.
Okay.
You know,
um,
you think
have my thanks and that Thanks of my family.
You saved my life.
I promise I won't waste it.
The machines must have come across.
Captain belongs patrol here.
I mean,
yeah,
one of the car just Soldiers fell here.
The other soldiers must have retreated.
That's aware
this card you fell far from the first battle.
At least his death came quickly.
Yeah.
Sons making a show of it.
Things can't be the helmet from the last card.
A soldier.
Someone nearly lost his head here, then ran off.
Yeah,
the
blood everywhere.
A machine dragged something into the water here.
Maybe he made it to that island.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Okay,
sure.
Mhm.
Blood everywhere.
Hm.
Mhm.
Mm.
But
yeah.
Uh huh.
Right.
Mhm
from
don't
he By this done by the sun I've never really done I brought down But it's not on the beach I went to the fair Found too many times to count I fingered every curl But I never won the girl by the sun By the sun I've never really done If they
I wasn't expecting to be found Especially not by a Nora I wasn't expecting to find a half clad card in soldiers singing like a drunk I apologize for my behavior.
I thought I was dead.
Come on.
Your commander asked me to bring you back to date.
Our I refuse to be led back to my outpost by Nora like some prisoner.
Fine.
Go by yourself.
Wait.
Look, I got in a tussle with a snap, Ma.
It ate the half of me.
That was armor and bow.
The thief is still in the water.
I can't go back without a weapon.
Find my bow, please.
I'll get it.
Just don't start singing again,
okay?
Yeah.
Better watch out for that machine.
It wasn't offended.
Then
snap, Ma Weakness to fire plays storage canister free sack destroying This component disables arranged freeze attack and triggers an explosion.
Eugene?
Yeah,
Okay.
Mhm.
Their attention.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
You know something?
Yes.
My hands
that hurt it
E yeah.
Through.
Yeah,
yeah, Yes.
Please, man.
Okay.
Yes.
What?
That's right.
Yeah.
Stock market,
E.
They're angry
about that.
Well,
yeah,
right.
Yeah.
Yes.
Might regret this.
Yeah.
Here's your bow.
Good luck out there.
Thank you.
I e didn't want to die in foreign lands like my men.
May the sun Like they're passing.
I mean,
yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
You will be for
shopping.
He didn't get immediate unit,
right?
Yeah,
yeah,
Yeah.
You think?
Okay, people.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's
also I just realized something was lost.
Okay.
Yeah.
Got one.
Great.
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you.
Oh.
Oh,
Mhm.
Yeah,
yeah,
but
okay.
All right.
Here we go again.
Yeah.
Everyone
just like that.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Back to your business.
Okay.
Thank you.
Mhm.
Yeah,
nothing but trouble.
That's all there is in but new glands turnover and also anything
genuine craftsmanship.
I've got all the best goods here
cost you a shar.
Just a look.
Look here came back on his own.
A little words for where he seemed a bit embarrassed when I mentioned you.
Dare I ask?
He has a lovely singing voice.
That's a capital life I've ever heard.
One.
I'll have a talk with him about it.
What is this place exactly?
Data are marks the eastern edge of cardio territory trading post a way station one with an ugly reputation among your people.
During the reign of the last son King, many Nora would taken captive, then gathered here for transport to Meridian and sacrifice.
But the sun set on it.
I was appointed by the Sun King of Odd To make sure old Carter at this outpost show respect to the Nora.
Did a nostrum named Oland come through here twice?
It was part of the royal delegation to the Nora when they passed through on the way them back.
My brought back stories of a vicious attack on your people.
My condolences, of course.
Something of odd wants peace.
So did the matriarchs, I'm told.
But old wounds are slow to mend on both tribes of proud.
My task is to make sure there are no further provocations from the Sunday Um, especially now after well, while your people recover from this terrible attack.
I mean, do you know where Olin is now?
Not exactly.
But he was on his way to Meridian.
I'm certain of that.
Everyone goes to Meridian.
There's a change place, a living city.
Nothing like it was during the rule of Sun King Giron.
Avada.
Our new king has done all he can to make sure that slavery is being abolished.
There's a new alliance with the Haram on the sun ring where so many outlanders were killed.
Isn't how memorial to the fallen Madsen King Giron raided the as Iran for years.
Abad managed to get them on his side.
We had help, of course.
Ursa and Aaron played a part.
Osram siblings bigger than life.
They gathered an army to free meridian.
I marched with um, scaled the north cliff with my men and secured the Temple of the sun sent Geron's Kestral Zen priest packing.
Now as a Rahmah, a common sight in the city on a common sound too sure bicker a lot.
It sounds as though you approve of the new Sun King.
He is the chosen of the sun on what the Sunda needs after 10 years of war, the calming light, not a scouring one.
Some king Geron would shed blood at any slight for some king of odd.
That's a last resort.
Lucky for those who slide him.
Some whisper in the shadows that he's weak.
No, peace is strength as the sun shall show.
Is there anything more you can tell me about The road to Meridian?
Sunk in Nevada's devoted considerable resources to making it safe.
But by the sun's witnesses being harder to control in peace than it was during the war, machines grow more dangerous all the time.
And to that, bandits and new reports of this corruption was stretched in to protect a few outposts like this one.
That's for everywhere else.
Well, traveling your own risk.
You said something happened with Nicola.
The Nor a girl.
Yes, something happened.
Attempted murder.
Prefect's IE can tell you more about it.
You can find him near the main tower up the steps.
Wait.
Saeed is here he is.
Look, I've heard what your people say about him, but he swears it's a case of mistaken identity.
If there's a shadow to him, I've never been able to prove it on the forbearance he showed towards this new car.
Woman was impressive.
Oh, speak to him.
Maybe he knows where she went and try not to assault in place.
Okay.
Is that really all you have?
Don't do it all.
All right.
Those shadow car just scum are gonna pay for what they did to IRSA.
I heard that a serum merchants charges double or even triple of what they charge their own tribe.
Mm.
Hope I don't catch a chill.
A spring in your step today,
Nora has He's been suspicious of outsiders.
I suppose they had good reason.
Okay.
It's
all those savages I don't like.
The longer this split with the shadow card that costs, the more prices will.
Okay.
Yeah,
e.
That's interesting.
Mhm.
I utterly refused to buy from a Nocera.
He'll cheat you soon as look at you.
The hunters launch should never admitted those women or savages.
It's a noble Carter institution.
Corruption spreads more sunless days are coming.
Okay?
Yes,
thank you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Watch out for the Oscar of merchants who seem cute.
You look at you.
So there are awesome.
I'm gonna send them now.
I get up by work.
Same as always,
years.
I'd And you're a Nora.
I can tell from your tone.
You've heard of me.
Let me ease your mind.
There seemed to be wild stories about me among your tribe.
But the Nora have me mistaken for someone else.
I'm not sure where the fault lies, but the fog of war often breeds confusion.
Unfortunately, some refused to acknowledge the Arab.
So itwas with the last Nora who came through here.
You mean Nicola?
Is that her name?
Oh, well, it was a very unfortunate situation.
She attacked me in broad daylight.
If one of my men hadn't spotted her, I might well have been injured.
But we were able to subdue her without harm.
What did you do with her?
I let her go.
Of course, it was clear she thought I was responsible for unspeakable things.
So in a sense, her actions were justifiable.
But all this nonsense about torture and murder that wasn't me.
They have me confused with some other commander.
I don't doubt some of my comrades did bad things, but Sun, king of Odd has worked hard to eliminate such brutality.
Where is Nicola now?
I don't know exactly.
She left raving that she would find a way to bring me down.
But I did hear a report from the garrison at Lonesome Rock that a young woman had been abducted by bandits might have been her.
You've really gone out of your way to help Prefect side.
It's no trouble.
The Sun King wishes to make amends with your people and I am his humble servant.
I'll goto Lonesome Rock and get to the bottom of this.
I promise you that you do that.
And if our men are anything less than helpful, please let me know.
Let your guard down
to destroy them.
Can't trust him.
Not after what your mom told me.
Back Garrison is my only lead.
Raised machines were Shaun's damn nonsense.
It's worse.
Always stay bright.
Always stay alert.
That's what I said.
We have to trust in our king.
Would you like to buy something today?
Options,
machines or bandits?
Try to get past me pipe.
Mark my words.
I face the sun's pride because I know I earned.
Yes, take a look at these wares.
Snow chill it just
fair price.
I hope you and your family are Well,
that's don't pass up these goods.
This is
I mean,
check out these wares.
Only the finest goods here.
See for yourself.
Good for Well,
Yeah.
All right.
Yeah,
Yeah.
The world beyond the sacred land.
I need to find Olen and learn everything.
He knows who the killers were, how they saw me through his focus.
The woman is one who looks like me.
Why they want me dead.
Poland's trail leads to Meridian.
When I catch him, he will talk
and he will pay for all the lives he's ruined.
You know what I mean?
Hello.
Our records show that you've been researching safe, comfortable, affordable apartments in the Salt Lake City area.
You should consider the record building.
Take a moment to review some of the features we offer our tenants.
Totally automated facility monitored by a bleeding at two.
Robotic security team.
Always comfy.
Biometric climate control, Auto.
Just the temperature of every room.
Complimentary Pharaoh runner.
Upon signing a lease, let your runner grab groceries and collect packages while you enjoy the luxury of the writer lifestyle are hollow side features a free, full immersive tour of the facilities, including a customizable mock up of your future Reicher apartment, Visit us today and start living
suspicious of outsiders.
I suppose they had good reason.
A guide to the claim by the well traveled our arm.
Often I fling open the windows of my villa not only to partake of the scents and sights of the city, but to hear the questions on the streets.
Equally often, I hear asked aloud what to make of these outsiders, these us Aram, who are suddenly our allies or even neighbors.
Why do they he does, they dio argue as they dio what is the matter of their heady scent?
Why are they always drinking like a ray of the sun?
Amid the darkness, a question is best followed to its source.
So for the benefit of the inquisitive, I contrive to join a trading caravan to the claim.
At least a Sfar is the closest village.
Beyond the break walls claim it is a muted land where fire smoke hangs heavy in the air.
Among the tall entries where the ground has not been dug up in the SRM ceaseless search for metal, it is cased in frost and beneath the frost.
Yet more frost before stony soil and worse soot everywhere, soot all pervading.
Though I had worn my sturdiest travel silks, keeping them on soiled proved impossible.
Noticing my discomfort, Samassa and Washerwomen offered their services.
But seeing the shade of the water in their tubs, I declined.
Indeed, regard for cleanliness is not a NASA and virtue.
Despite its protective walls of piled slate and slouched round stone huts, the village struck me as overly exposed to the elements, the chief elements in the claim being a cold, oily rain and whore frost.
Even so, the open fires hissed and spat and burned on, and the mood was bustling and lively, much as you might find in an outbuilding for livestock, for example, when I will endure to bring the light of knowledge to the folk of my tribe.
Thea's RM have no priests or kings and spit at the mention of such titles, but they differ to the council of their wise men, the village ill doorman.
It seems each settlement elects such men for the purpose of unceasing argument.
From dawn until long into the night, they shout over each other on matters of policy and taxation.
Come the next morning, a line of Villagers will already have formed for the privilege of arguing back.
I joined such a line for several hours while Children squealed, birds squawked and hammering a curse.
It endless hammering echoed over the trampled straw and rain filled Cartwrights.
Finally, I was permitted to face the three eel doorman and deliver my question.
I asked for their opinion on the peace between our tribes and some king of odds offer of welcome and meridian itself.
Readers, I say asked.
But the matter was not so simple as the author and erupted into insults and arguments even before the words had finished.
Leaving my lips, I found myself talked over, shouted down, subjected to seemingly unconnected abuse.
And it was only when I raised my voice in return and invigorating experience that I was grudgingly answered.
Their opinions are muddled and mixed, to say the least, and I will not profane this parchment by transcribing the words used to express them.
Suffice it to say that they see the benefit of free trade between our tribes and indeed have flourished from it.
After long years of war.
However, it seems few author and that trade outside the claim, return their taxes or even return it all.
The eel doorman believed their stolen away by a manner of living that is downright Kharja.
Ah, phrase they punctuate by spitting on the floor.
In return, I suggested that their mistrust and fear of a civilized way of life was positively.
Ah, sorry, um, I could not bring myself to spit indoors.
This caused great commotion, after which I was bodily, carried from the building upon the shoulders of my hosts and deposited in the midst of a coming of age celebration.
Not for a man, but for some new manner of device.
I woke on a cart arriving at pitch cliff.
My throat was horse.
My arms number from accepting countless challenges to wrestle and the taste of an alcohol much like machine oil was still on my tongue.
My headache tas if split down the center.
Truly, I had risked my life in search of an answer.
Is there more to the answer, Um, character than brawling, drinking and shouting?
Simply put, their reader there is not.
But let us hope that the eel Dorman's fears will be proven true, and in time, the sun's light and meridians glory can temper these rough hewn folk.
Watch out for the Oscar on merchants who seem cute.
She was.
Look at you
three.
What's wrong?
Esteemed lords and ladies of the Sun court honored cons and patrons your concerns regarding the continuing derangement of the machines, Air noted.
Though many seasons have passed since the first sightings of this frightful change, the Sun King is well aware that this is no longer a matter of reports from border patrols in Hunter's Lodge expeditions, one needs only look to the abandoned the state lands.
Indeed, the estates you owned left for the Jewell to reclaim or to the empty free holds of the common cards of folk.
You know that the Sun King has taken every measure to protect Holy Meridian in the maze lands with renewed patrols.
As for in treating the sun, we believe the cause of the derangement cannot be the sun's displeasure alone for the years of sacrifice.
Under Sun King, Giron produced no noticeable effect on the machines.
His luminous and the Sun priests are in agreement that even if this is an ordeal set for us by the sun.
Our suffering will not be reduced with blood.
For your edification, I will recount what we have observed of the derangement of the simpler machines that herd creatures the Gallup er's, the Scud Alors, where once they fled at the sight of men, now they're more likely to charge the larger creatures.
Once only a menace to the inebriated and foolhardy can be seen to lunch of the unwary with murderous intent.
This is to say nothing of the coming of the Sawtooth or its metal brethren the ravage er, the stalker or that terrible giant, the Thunder Jaw.
Each one has proved a more capable killer of men and the last each wielding a wider array of strange weapons.
The wilds air no longer safe due to the hostility of these new machines, though to date they have not attacked a settlement within the symptom.
Outlanders have brought no shortage of fanciful explanations for this behavior.
Some suggest that the machines have come to resent men for hunting them.
Yet such a thing has never been witnessed among beasts of flesh and blood, and they're proven to be more capable of thinking and memory Carta hunters and author and tinkers like have attempted to understand the phenomenon by inspecting felled machines.
But these appear no different to those harvested many years before derangement began with the same assortments of wires, braiding, lenses, hearts and so on.
When these parts are subjected to the light of the sun or to a ceramic Spehr immense with fire and spark, they react as they always have.
The band nook, however, claimed to have recorded a change in the machine songs of the machine spirits, suggesting that these have become increasingly discordant.
The Sun King has sent on voice to ban or toe learn more in the hopes that their mysticism might contain a truth when the rational light of the sun is brought to bear upon it.
Of course, the Sun King graciously welcomes your own contributions to study of the derangement, asking only that they are delivered in written form and not during royal audience.
His luminous also hopes to dissuade you from participating in machine hunts.
During these uncertain times.
The strength of a united son court is the strength of all Kharja respectful Tasha T court envoy
Yeah,
yeah,
Okay,